{"status":"Success","data":{"general_datas":[{"q_number":"65","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16."},{"q_number":"136","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f .\u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"137","question":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d15\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"138","question":"\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d7b, \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d34"},{"q_number":"139","question":"\u0d05\u0d7d\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7b, \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d7c \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d31\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d2c\u0d4d "},{"q_number":"140","question":"\u0d26 \u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d07\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f"},{"q_number":"141","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02"},{"q_number":"142","question":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d3e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d2d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d09\u0d31\u0d41\u0d26\u0d41"},{"q_number":"143","question":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d7b?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"144","question":"e - reading \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d e, \u0d15\u0d4a\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"electronic"},{"q_number":"145","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?\t","answer":"\u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"146","question":"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ,\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d05\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\u0d25\u0d02 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d36\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d16\u0d41\u0d7c\u0d06\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"147","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"148","question":"\u0d24\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d4d \u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d7b \u0d06\u0d32\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d"},{"q_number":"149","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d0e\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d28\u0d40\u0d32\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d42\u0d7c (\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2f\u0d02)"},{"q_number":"150","question":"\u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d47\u0d2a \u0d35\u0d47\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02"},{"q_number":"151","question":"\u0d35\u0d40\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d42\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"152","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?\t","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d7b"},{"q_number":"153","question":"\u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27 \u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d7c"},{"q_number":"154","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d?","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"155","question":"\u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d41\u0d03\u0d16\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40 \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d02, \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e?","answer":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d1a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"156","question":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24 \r\n"},{"q_number":"157","question":"\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d38\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"158","question":"\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e: \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d41\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"160","question":"\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d.\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d31\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"161","question":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d12.\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d.\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d26\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d18 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d09\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"162","question":". \" \u0d35\u0d46\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d02 \u0d26\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b \u0d38\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d26\u0d02\" \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d08 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d02 \r\n"},{"q_number":"163","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d15 \u0d38\u0d39\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"164","question":"\"\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"165","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \"\u0d35\u0d40\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d35\u0d4d\" \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"166","question":"\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d1f\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d41\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \"\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d41\u0d15\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d\" \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d40\u0d15\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"1958 \r\n"},{"q_number":"167","question":"\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d15\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d4b\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d28\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d2c\u0d4b\u0d27\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \r\n"},{"q_number":"168","question":". \"\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"169","question":"\"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"170","question":". \"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"171","question":"\"\u0d07\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46 \u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"172","question":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d17\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d31\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"173","question":"\"\u0d0e\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d02\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d1f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"174","question":"\u0d0f\u0d24\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2d\u0d17\u0d35\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d40\u0d24 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d02 \r\n"},{"q_number":"175","question":"18. \r\n\r\n\"\u0d26\u0d36\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30 \u0d1a\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d26\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"176","question":"\u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \"\u0d2d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d4d\" \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02 \r\n"},{"q_number":"177","question":"\u0d38\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d42\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d47\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d02 \r\n"},{"q_number":"178","question":". \"\u0d38\u0d42\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\" \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d32\u0d47\u0d16 \r\n"},{"q_number":"179","question":"\"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46\" \u0d06\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d24\u0d41\u0d30\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"180","question":". \"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"181","question":"\"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d4c\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2f\" \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d02\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d15\u0d30\u0d23\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d40\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d32\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"182","question":"\"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d34\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d47\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d41\u0d17\u0d24\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"183","question":"\"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41\u0d1a\u0d42\u0d21\u0d28\u0d4d (\u0d38\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d32\u0d3f)\r\n"},{"q_number":"184","question":". \"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\" \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d30\u0d4d \r\n"},{"q_number":"185","question":"\"\u0d17\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\" \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d3f\u0d1c\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d02 \u0d05\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d28\u0d1f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d3f\u0d02\u0d17\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d3f \r\n"},{"q_number":"188","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d '\u0d0f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d25\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7b \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d7b' ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d2f\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"189","question":"\u0d08 \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d7a\u0d35\u0d46\u0d7d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d36\u0d7c \u0d15\u0d41\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d7c\u0d23\u0d3f (\u0d15\u0d57 \u0d06\u0d7b\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"524","question":"\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d34\u0d35\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d3f. \u0d15\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\r\n"},{"q_number":"525","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\r\n"},{"q_number":"526","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d2e\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4b\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"527","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d38\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d21\u0d4b.\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"528","question":"\u0d24\u0d15\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d40\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"529","question":"\u0d38\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d05\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"530","question":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"531","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"532","question":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e.\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d09\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d41\r\n"},{"q_number":"533","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d46 \u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d0e\u0d02\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"534","question":"\u0d35\u0d48\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d02\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d39\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d37\u0d40\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d05\u0d31\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"535","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d28\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d32 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46. \u0d2c\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"536","question":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d02\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"537","question":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d1b\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d12. \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d35\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"538","question":"\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d.\u0d15\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d32\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"539","question":"\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d17\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"540","question":"\u0d0e\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d36\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"541","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d13\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d08\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"542","question":"\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"543","question":"\u0d2f\u0d41.\u0d0e\u0d16\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"544","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d(1911)\r\n"},{"q_number":"545","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d1f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23 \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33\r\n"},{"q_number":"546","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d4d\u200c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d32\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1c\u0d28\u0d02\r\n"},{"q_number":"547","question":"\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d.\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33, \u0d38\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"548","question":"\u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d0e\u0d02\u0d2a\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d, \u0d07.\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d, \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"549","question":"\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d46 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d07.\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d43\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33, \u0d15\u0d46.\u0d38\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\r\n"},{"q_number":"550","question":"\u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e \u0d07\u0d32\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"551","question":"\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d41\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d42\u0d1f\u0d46\r\n"},{"q_number":"552","question":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21\u0d32\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"553","question":"\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d15\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d, \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d2f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f \u0d07\u0d35 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"554","question":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d32\u0d41\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\r\n"},{"q_number":"555","question":"\u0d2a\u0d3f. \u0d35\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d34\u0d32\u0d41\u0d31\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d34\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e(1975)\r\n"},{"q_number":"556","question":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d23\u0d7b \u0d28\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02, \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d23\u0d2f\u0d17\u0d40\u0d24\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e, \u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d35\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d41\u0d16\u0d2e\u0d46\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46, \u0d05\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4a\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d2f"},{"q_number":"557","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d35\u0d30\u0d23 \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d (2010\u0d7d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"558","question":"\u0d39\u0d48\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d24 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d7d - \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d02.\u0d2a\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d40\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\r\n"},{"q_number":"559","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d41\u0d15 \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d02 \u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\r\n"},{"q_number":"560","question":"\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"561","question":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3f \u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d47\u0d7d\r\n"},{"q_number":"562","question":"\u0d2c\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d7c\u0d37\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"2009 (\u0d06\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02)\r\n"},{"q_number":"563","question":"\u0d06\u0d35\u0d47 \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d41\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d46.\u0d06\u0d7c \u0d2e\u0d40\u0d30(2009\u0d7d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"574","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d02, \u0d35\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d3f, \u0d2c\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d28\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d7b\u0d15\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d, \u0d17\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 "},{"q_number":"575","question":"\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"1999\r\n"},{"q_number":"576","question":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d40\u0d30\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d2e\u0d34\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d41\u0d02, \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d1c\u0d40\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d02, \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2e\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d41\u0d24\u0d47, \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f, \u0d06\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d30\u0d42\u0d2a\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d7d, \u0d38\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 "},{"q_number":"577","question":"\u0d21\u0d4b. \u0d0e\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d40\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d7e ?\r\n","answer":"*\u0d13\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d (1978), *\u0d15\u0d47\u0d30\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d (1980), *\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d(1986"},{"q_number":"578","question":"\u0d39\u0d43\u0d26\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d19\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"579","question":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d41\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b \u0d24\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d34\u0d7d \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"2010\u0d7d, \u0d05\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d12\u0d30\u0d41 \u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d41\r\n"},{"q_number":"580","question":"\u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d15\u0d46\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d41\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d33\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d13\u0d31\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d48\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"581","question":"\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d25\u0d2e \u0d1f\u0d3e\u0d17\u0d4b\u0d7c \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d?\r\n","answer":"2010\u0d7d\r\n"},{"q_number":"582","question":"2010\u0d7d , \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f '\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d41 \u0d2c\u0d46\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ' \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a '\u0d38\u0d40\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d2e\u0d46\u0d7b' \u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41 \u0d1c\u0d4b\u0d38\u0d2b\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"583","question":"\u0d07\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d15\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d7d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d09\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d24\u0d3f \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7b\r\n"},{"q_number":"584","question":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"1828 \u0d06\u0d17\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d 28(\u0d38\u0d46\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 9- \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d32\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d7c \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02)\r\n"},{"q_number":"585","question":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1f\u0d46?\r\n","answer":"\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d\r\n"},{"q_number":"586","question":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"1910 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 7\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"587","question":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d27\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d35\u0d41\u0d02(1869), \u0d05\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d30\u0d47\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28, \u0d07\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d7b \u0d07\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d23\u0d02, \u0d2e\u0d28\u0d41\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d28\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d2d\u0d42\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d47\u0d23\u0d02, \u0d05\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4b\u0d7e \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d02 "},{"q_number":"588","question":"\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d4a \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d7e\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d7d \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d36\u0d48\u0d36\u0d35\u0d02(1852), \u0d15\u0d57\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02(1854), \u0d2f\u0d57\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d28\u0d02(1857)\r\n"},{"q_number":"589","question":"\u0d06\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d7b \u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d16\u0d4b\u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 (\u0d31\u0d37\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d7b \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d7b) \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d36\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d15\u0d7e?\r\n","answer":"\u0d26\u0d4d \u0d1a\u0d46\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d13\u0d7c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d21\u0d4d, \u0d26\u0d4d \u0d38\u0d40\u0d17\u0d7e, \u0d05\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e \u0d35\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2f, \u0d26\u0d4d \u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40 \u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d.\r\n"},{"q_number":"590","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"1835 \u0d28\u0d35\u0d02\u0d2c\u0d7c 30\u0d28\u0d4d(\u0d2f\u0d41 \u0d0e\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d0e\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d2b\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d4b\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d21\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7d)\r\n"},{"q_number":"591","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2f\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d25 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d38\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d35\u0d47\u0d7d \u0d32\u0d3e\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d39\u0d4b\u0d7a \u0d15\u0d4d\u0d32\u0d2e\u0d7b\u0d38\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"592","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d7b \u0d2e\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d24\u0d46\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"1910 \u0d0f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d7d 21\u0d28\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"593","question":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d7c\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d27\u0d3e\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d7e ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d39\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d7e\u0d2c\u0d31\u0d3f \u0d2b\u0d3f\u0d7b,\u0d26\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d21\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d47\u0d34\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d1f\u0d4b\u0d02 \u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2f\u0d7c, \u0d32\u0d48\u0d2b\u0d4d \u0d13\u0d7a \u0d2e\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f.\r\n"},{"q_number":"612","question":"\u0d15\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d3f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d4d \u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d25\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d09\u0d2a\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1b\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"613","question":"\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d02 \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d15\u0d25\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1e\u0d30\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"614","question":"\u0d15\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d05\u0d31\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2a\u0d3f.\u0d35\u0d3f. \u0d05\u0d2f\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"615","question":"\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d07\u0d1f\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d36\u0d47\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d17\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"616","question":"\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d02 \u0d32\u0d2d\u0d3f\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d1c\u0d3f. \u0d36\u0d19\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d30\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d31\u0d41\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"622","question":"\u0d2e\u0d27\u0d41\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d32 \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46(\u0d15\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d24) \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d39\u0d30\u0d3f \u0d35\u0d02\u0d36\u0d4d \u0d31\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d2c\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"623","question":"\u0d15\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d28\u0d4b\u0d35\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d41\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d4d \u0d30\u0d3e\u0d1c\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d28\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\r\n"},{"q_number":"624","question":"\u0d38\u0d02\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d43\u0d24 \u0d28\u0d3e\u0d1f\u0d15\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d0e\u0d34\u0d41\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"625","question":"\u0d1a\u0d32\u0d1a\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d46\u0d1f\u0d4d\u0d1f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d15\u0d43\u0d24\u0d3f ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d21 \u0d35\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d2e\u0d4d\u0d2e\r\n"},{"q_number":"626","question":"\u0d38\u0d4b\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d24\u0d42\u0d32\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d24\u0d4b\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\r\n"},{"q_number":"651","question":"\u0d1c\u0d4d\u0d1e\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d2a\u0d40\u0d20\u0d02 \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d06\u0d36\u0d3e\u0d2a\u0d42\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d23\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d47\u0d35\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"652","question":"\u0d15\u0d47\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30 \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d05\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d26\u0d2e\u0d3f \u0d05\u0d35\u0d3e\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\u0d21\u0d4d \u0d28\u0d47\u0d1f\u0d3f\u0d2f \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d35\u0d28\u0d3f\u0d24 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d05\u0d2e\u0d43\u0d24\u0d2a\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d24\u0d02 ( \u0d2a\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3e\u0d2c\u0d4d )\r\n"},{"q_number":"656","question":"'\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d1e\u0d4d\u0d1a\u0d3f \u0d15\u0d4b\u0d21\u0d4d ' \u0d0e\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d21\u0d3e\u0d28\u0d4d\u200d \u0d2c\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d4c\u0d23\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"658","question":"\u0d06\u0d30\u0d41\u0d1f\u0d46 \u0d1c\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d23\u0d4d \u0d32\u0d4b\u0d15 \u0d2a\u0d41\u0d38\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d15 \u0d26\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d2f\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d1a\u200c\u0d30\u0d3f\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d15\u0d41\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d28\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 \u0d37\u0d47\u0d15\u0d4d\u200c\u0d38\u0d4d\u200c\u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d2f\u0d30\u0d4d\u200d\r\n"},{"q_number":"663","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d0f\u0d15\u0d2d\u0d3e\u0d37\u0d3e \u0d28\u0d3f\u0d18\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d1f\u0d41\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d31\u0d46 \u0d30\u0d1a\u0d2f\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d \u0d06\u0d30\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d40\u0d15\u0d23\u0d4d\u0d20\u0d47\u0d36\u0d4d\u0d35\u0d30\u0d02 \u0d2a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2e\u0d28\u0d3e\u0d2d \u0d2a\u0d3f\u0d33\u0d4d\u0d33"},{"q_number":"664","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f \u0d38\u0d3e\u0d39\u0d3f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d2e\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d15 \u0d0f\u0d24\u0d4d ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d3f\u0d28\u0d3f"},{"q_number":"665","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d32\u0d15\u0d4d\u0d37\u0d23\u0d2e\u0d4a\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24 \u0d2e\u0d39\u0d3e\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02 ?\r\n","answer":"\u0d30\u0d3e\u0d2e\u0d1a\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d30\u0d35\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d3e\u0d38\u0d02"},{"q_number":"666","question":"\u0d2e\u0d32\u0d2f\u0d3e\u0d33\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d3f\u0d32\u0d46 \u0d06\u0d26\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d24\u0d4d\u0d24\u0d46 \u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d15\u0d3e\u0d35\u0d4d\u0d2f\u0d02?\r\n","answer":"\u0d2e\u0d2f\u0d42\u0d30\u0d38\u0d28\u0d4d\u0d26\u0d47\u0d36\u0d02"}]},"code":"100"}